{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Brick \u0026 Stone Patio Repair Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40801/":{"taskOID":40801,"originalTaskOID":40801,"setID":759,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4097,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Stone","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of stone needs repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3611,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Limestone","answerDisplayText":"Limestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5481,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sandstone","answerDisplayText":"Sandstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5776,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Slate","answerDisplayText":"Slate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1466,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cobblestone","answerDisplayText":"Cobblestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2500,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Flagstone","answerDisplayText":"Flagstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4867,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Interlocking  concrete pavers","answerDisplayText":"Pre-formed interlocking concrete pavers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4987,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Quartz","answerDisplayText":"Quartz","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10315,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6990,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Area","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of area needs repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10596,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10597,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pool Surround","answerDisplayText":"Pool Surround","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10598,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Seating area","answerDisplayText":"Seating area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10599,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Walkway","answerDisplayText":"Walkway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10600,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Home entryway","answerDisplayText":"Home entryway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10601,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Driveway/parking","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/parking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4098,"questionDisplayText":"Description of Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Describe the problem(s) you need repaired.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1187,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bulging","answerDisplayText":"Bulging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1703,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cracks","answerDisplayText":"Cracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1940,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1902,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Deteriorating mortar joints","answerDisplayText":"Deteriorating mortar joints","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3521,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Leaning wall","answerDisplayText":"Leaning wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3659,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Loose brick, stone or block","answerDisplayText":"Loose brick, stone or block","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5744,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Sinking or settling (low spot)","answerDisplayText":"Sinking or settling (low spot)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3488,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Leaching water","answerDisplayText":"Leaching water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6609,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Unstable","answerDisplayText":"Unstable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5428,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Rotten wood pieces","answerDisplayText":"Rotten wood pieces","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4097,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Stone","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of stone needs repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3611,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Limestone","answerDisplayText":"Limestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5481,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sandstone","answerDisplayText":"Sandstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5776,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Slate","answerDisplayText":"Slate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1466,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cobblestone","answerDisplayText":"Cobblestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2500,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Flagstone","answerDisplayText":"Flagstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4867,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Interlocking  concrete pavers","answerDisplayText":"Pre-formed interlocking concrete pavers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4987,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Quartz","answerDisplayText":"Quartz","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10315,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3611,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Limestone","answerDisplayText":"Limestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5481,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sandstone","answerDisplayText":"Sandstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5776,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Slate","answerDisplayText":"Slate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1466,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cobblestone","answerDisplayText":"Cobblestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2500,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Flagstone","answerDisplayText":"Flagstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4867,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Interlocking  concrete pavers","answerDisplayText":"Pre-formed interlocking concrete pavers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4987,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Quartz","answerDisplayText":"Quartz","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10315,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6990,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Area","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of area needs repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10596,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10597,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pool Surround","answerDisplayText":"Pool Surround","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10598,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Seating area","answerDisplayText":"Seating area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10599,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Walkway","answerDisplayText":"Walkway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10600,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Home entryway","answerDisplayText":"Home entryway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10601,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Driveway/parking","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/parking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10596,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10597,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pool Surround","answerDisplayText":"Pool Surround","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10598,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Seating area","answerDisplayText":"Seating area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10599,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Walkway","answerDisplayText":"Walkway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10600,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Home entryway","answerDisplayText":"Home entryway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10601,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Driveway/parking","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/parking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4098,"questionDisplayText":"Description of Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Describe the problem(s) you need repaired.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1187,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bulging","answerDisplayText":"Bulging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1703,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cracks","answerDisplayText":"Cracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1940,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1902,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Deteriorating mortar joints","answerDisplayText":"Deteriorating mortar joints","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3521,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Leaning wall","answerDisplayText":"Leaning wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3659,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Loose brick, stone or block","answerDisplayText":"Loose brick, stone or block","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5744,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Sinking or settling (low spot)","answerDisplayText":"Sinking or settling (low spot)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3488,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Leaching water","answerDisplayText":"Leaching water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6609,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Unstable","answerDisplayText":"Unstable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5428,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Rotten wood pieces","answerDisplayText":"Rotten wood pieces","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1187,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bulging","answerDisplayText":"Bulging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1703,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cracks","answerDisplayText":"Cracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1940,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1902,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Deteriorating mortar joints","answerDisplayText":"Deteriorating mortar joints","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3521,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Leaning wall","answerDisplayText":"Leaning wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3659,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Loose brick, stone or block","answerDisplayText":"Loose brick, stone or block","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5744,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Sinking or settling (low spot)","answerDisplayText":"Sinking or settling (low spot)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3488,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Leaching water","answerDisplayText":"Leaching water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6609,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Unstable","answerDisplayText":"Unstable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5428,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Rotten wood pieces","answerDisplayText":"Rotten wood pieces","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40801/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40801,"taskName":"Brick and Stone Flatwork -  Repair","taskDescription":"Repair Brick or Stone Flatwork","xmTaskDescriptor":"Brick \u0026 Stone Patio Repair Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":287,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Brick Stone Patios Steps flooring","textMessagingName":"Rep Mason Flatwork","rolloverLongDesc":"Most brick \u0026 stone flatwork has mortared joints, though sometimes brickwork \u0026 often concrete pavers are installed using a dry method where sand is brushed into the cracks. Note that stone tiles are covered under separate tile work categories.","rolloverShortDesc":"For cracks, discoloration, bulging, loose joints, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Brick or Stone Patios, Walks, and Steps.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Brick Patio Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Stone Patio Repair","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":16,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Brick \u0026 Stone Flatwork Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Brick \u0026 Stone Flatwork - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Brick and Stone Project","urlName":"Brick-and-Stone-Patios-Walks-and-Steps-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Brick \u0026 Stone Patio Repair Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Brick \u0026 Stone Step Repair","searchKeywords":"Brick,Stone,Patios,Steps,flooring,stones,bricks,mason,architect,landscape,build,concrete,driveways,cobblestone,wall,walkway,stairs,sidewalks,pavers,masonry,floor,Walks","emcCategoryOid":-12008,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":759,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}